{"nodeID":10,"children":[{"nodeID":6,"children":[{"nodeID":4,"children":[{"nodeID":2,"children":[{"nodeID":0,"children":[],"question":"Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper","infoDesc":"Render call expected"},{"nodeID":1,"children":[],"question":"Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper","infoDesc":"Render call not expected"}],"question":"Is a render expected to take place?","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper","infoDesc":"Component mutates state"},{"nodeID":3,"children":[],"question":"Is a render expected to take place?","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper","infoDesc":"Component does not mutates state"}],"question":"Is this component mutating the state?","thisAnswer":"Function","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html","infoDesc":"Component Type: Function"},{"nodeID":5,"children":[],"question":"Is this component mutating the state?","thisAnswer":"Class","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html","infoDesc":"Component Type: Class"}],"question":"Is the bug in a function component or a class component?","thisAnswer":"React","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components","infoDesc":"Framework used: React"},{"nodeID":7,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Angular","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Angular"},{"nodeID":8,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Vue.js","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Vue.js"},{"nodeID":9,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Gatsby.js","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Gatsby.js"}],"question":"What framework or technology is being used?","thisAnswer":null,"nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_framework","infoDesc":null}